{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Enterprise Architecture",
    "Term": "Midterms",
    "Title": "QUIZ REVIEWER FOR MIDTERMS",
    "LastModified": "20 October 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "03_Handout_1 and 04_Handout_1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is TRUE  about a communication diagram?",
      "answer": "It describes the interactions among classes in terms of an exchange of messages overtime",
      "choices": [
        "It illustrates the dynamic nature of a system by modeling the flow of control from activity to activity",
        "It is a unit of collective technological behavior collaboratively performed by two or more nodes",
        "It describes the interactions among classes in terms of an exchange of messages overtime",
        "It models the interactions between objects in sequence"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In technological behavior concepts, which of the following statements is TRUE  about technology interaction?",
      "answer": "It is a unit of collective technological behavior collaboratively performed by two or more nodes.",
      "choices": [
        "It is a unit of collective technological behavior collaboratively performed by two or more nodes.",
        "It is a sequence of technological behavior that achieves a specific outcome",
        "It is an external visible unit of functionality, provided by one or more nodes accessible through well-defined interfaces",
        "It is a technology behavior element that denotes a state change"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It refers to a precisely defined outcome of a work package, in relation with implementation and migration.",
      "answer": "Deliverable",
      "choices": [
        "Deliverable",
        "Work Package",
        "Plateau",
        "Gap"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about architecture description language?",
      "answer": "This is commonly used by database developers but not generally used by programmers",
      "choices": [
        "This is commonly used by database developers but not generally used by programmers",
        "It is a general term referring to different formal languages in enabling formalization and description of a software architectures",
        "It is a wide variety of ADLs exist, with several differences in the exact concepts it offer, and are mainly suitable for users with technical background",
        "Some examples are UniCon, Wright, and Acme"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This pertains to an individual, team, department, or organization that represents an interest in the architecture's outcome.",
      "answer": "Stakeholder",
      "choices": [
        "Stakeholder",
        "Driver",
        "Business Role",
        "Business Actor"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In enterprise architecture motivational concepts, which of the following best describes an organizational value?",
      "answer": "It is the relative worth, usefulness, or importance of a core element or an outcome",
      "choices": [
        "It is the relative worth, usefulness, or importance of a core element or an outcome",
        "It is a result that has been achieved",
        "It is a factor that averts or hinders the realization of goals",
        "It is a high-level statement of intent, direction, or an end state of an organization"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about gateways, in relation with business process diagrams?",
      "answer": "It is a sub-part of a pool",
      "choices": [
        "It is a decision point that can adjust the path based on conditions or events",
        "It is a sub-part of a pool",
        "It is a gateway can be exclusive or inclusive, parallel, complex",
        "It is a gateway can be based on data or event"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is TRUE  about a state machine diagram?",
      "answer": "It describes the dynamic behavior of a system in response to external stimuli",
      "choices": [
        "It describes the dynamic behavior of a system in response to external stimuli",
        "It models the interactions between objects in sequence",
        "It illustrates the dynamic nature of a system by modeling the flow of control from activity to activity",
        "It is a unit of collective technological behavior collaboratively performed by two or more nodes"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This provides a further explanation of a specific part of a business process modeling notation diagram.",
      "answer": "Annotation",
      "choices": [
        "Annotation",
        "Activity",
        "Data Object",
        "Group"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This type of business process modeling notation element includes sub-processes, loops, and compensations",
      "answer": "Activity",
      "choices": [
        "Annotation",
        "Activity",
        "Data Object",
        "Group"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In enterprise architecture motivational concepts, which of the following best describes an organizational goal?",
      "answer": "It is a high-level statement of intent, direction, or an end state of an organization",
      "choices": [
        "It is the relative worth, usefulness, or importance of a core element or an outcome",
        "It is a result that has been achieved",
        "It is a factor that averts or hinders the realization of goals",
        "It is a high-level statement of intent, direction, or an end state of an organization"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In technological behavior concepts, which of the following statements is TRUE  about a technology process",
      "answer": "It is a sequence of technological behaviors that achieves a specific outcome",
      "choices": [
        "It is a sequence of technological behaviors that achieves a specific outcome",
        "It is a behavior element that groups infrastructural behavior, which can be performed by a node",
        "It is an external visible unit of functionality, provided by one or more nodes accessible through well-defined interfaces",
        "It is a technology behavior element that denotes a state change"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In business sturcture concepts, it refers to an entity that is capable of performing behaviors.",
      "answer": "Business Actor",
      "choices": [
        "Business Actor",
        "Business Role",
        "Driver",
        "Stakeholder"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following statements best describes the unified modeling language?",
      "answer": "It emerged from the combination of three existing practices/techniques",
      "choices": [
        "It emerged from the combination of three existing practices/techniques",
        "It is a general term referring to different formal languages in enabling formalization and description of a software architectures",
        "It is a wide variety of ADLs exist, with several differences in the exact concepts it offer, and are mainly suitable for users with technical background",
        "Some examples are UniCon, Wright, and Acme"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "What dies ADL stand for?",
      "answer": "Architecture Description Language",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Description Language",
        "Architecture Descriptive Language",
        "Advanced Description Language",
        "Advanced Descriptive Language"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is an external or internal condition that motivates an organization to define its goals",
      "answer": "Driver",
      "choices": [
        "Driver",
        "Meaning",
        "Principle",
        "Outcome"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This sub-model in a business process modeling notation diagram occurs between a private process and an external participant.",
      "answer": "Abstract Business Process",
      "choices": [
        "Abstract Business Process",
        "Private Business Process",
        "Collaborative Business Process",
        "Public Business Process"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which if the following is NOT a valid statement about events, in relation with business process diagrams?",
      "answer": "It provides a further explanation of the specific parts of a diagram",
      "choices": [
        "It provides a further explanation of the specific parts of a diagram",
        "It is a trigger that starts, modifies, or completes a process",
        "It include message, timer, error, compensation, signal, cancel, escalation, link",
        "It can be classified as either \"throwing\" or \"catching\""
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes a plateau in implementation and migration concepts?",
      "answer": "It is a relatively stable state of an enterprise architecture that exists during a specific period",
      "choices": [
        "It is a relatively stable state of an enterprise architecture that exists during a specific period",
        "It is a precisely defined outcome of a work package",
        "It is a behavior element that denotes a state of change related to implementation",
        "It is a series of actions identified and designed to achieve a specific goal or result"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "There are assets owned and/or controlled by an individual or an organization and are commonly assigned to capabilities.",
      "answer": "Resources",
      "choices": [
        "Resources",
        "Capabilities",
        "Course Of Action",
        "Strategies"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In structural unified modeling language diagrams, which of the following statements best describes a package diagram?",
      "answer": "It is a subset of a class diagram that organizes elements of a system into related groups",
      "choices": [
        "It is a subset of a class diagram that organizes elements of a system into related groups",
        "It describes the static structure of a system",
        "It describes the organization of physical software components",
        "It depicts the physical resources in a system"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In an enterprise, it is an approach or plan for configuring capabilities and resources undertaken to achieve a goal.",
      "answer": "Course Of Action",
      "choices": [
        "Course Of Action",
        "Capabilities",
        "Resources",
        "Strategies"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This element shows the logical arrangement of activities but does not change the diagram's flow",
      "answer": "Group",
      "choices": [
        "Group",
        "Data object",
        "Object",
        "Dynamic"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does UML stand for?",
      "answer": "Unified Modeling Language",
      "choices": [
        "Unified Modeling Language",
        "Unity Modeling Language",
        "Unified Markup Language",
        "Unity Markup Language"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This behavioral unified modeling language diagram describes the dynamic behavior of a system in response to external stimuli.",
      "answer": "State machine diagram",
      "choices": [
        "State machine diagram",
        "Use case diagram",
        "Timing diagram",
        "Sequence diagram"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In structural unified modeling language diagrams, which of the following statements best describes a component diagram",
      "answer": "It describes the organization of the physical and software aspects of a system",
      "choices": [
        "It describes the organization of the physical and software aspects of a system",
        "It shows the internal parts of a class",
        "It describes the static structure of a system",
        "It describes the static structure of a system at a particular time"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This refers to a unit of collective business behavior collaboratively performed by two or more business roles.",
      "answer": "Business Interaction",
      "choices": [
        "Business Interaction",
        "Business Event",
        "Business Function",
        "Business Service"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements best describes the architecture description language?",
      "answer": "It is a general term referring to different formal languages in enabling formalization and description of a software architectures.",
      "choices": [
        "It is a general term referring to different formal languages in enabling formalization and description of a software architectures.",
        "It is currently the most important industry-standard language for specifying, visualizing, constructing, and documenting",
        "It is commonly used by programmers, but not generally used by database developers",
        "It emerged from the combination of three existing practices"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    }
  ]
}